 [
        {"id":"1",
        "Question": " How much sugar is in D’s Energy drinks? ",
        "Answer": "There are 55 grams per serving. Maintaining a healthy and well-balanced lifestyle is important to D’s Energy Drinks. Our beverages are perfect for athletes and those who maintain an active lifestyle. Check with your doctor before consuming if you have dietary concerns. "
         },
    {  "id":"2",
       "Question": " How do I turn on my TV?",
       "Answer": "We provide a remote control with each of our TVs. Click the ON button, and you’ll be good to go! "
    },
    {  "id":"3",
       "Question": "What Are frequently Asked Questions?",
       "Answer": "Frequently asked questions (FAQ) are questions and answers that follow a certain topic – a collection of common questions that tend to be asked repeatedly on issues such as timing, delivery, handling, product information, and return policy. FAQs can be anywhere on the page, most commonly at the top or bottom."
    },
    {  "id":"4",
        "Question": "Are FAQs frequently answered questions?",
       "Answer": "The purpose of a FAQ is generally to provide information on frequent questions or concerns; however, the format is a useful means of organizing information, and text consisting of questions and their answers may thus be called a FAQ regardless of whether the questions are actually frequently asked."
    },
    {  "id":"5",
        "Question": "What is FAQ full form?",
        "Answer": "frequently asked questions. ' (a list of questions and answers about a particular subject, especially one giving basic information for users of a website)"
    },
    {   "id":"6",
        "Question": "How long should FAQ answers be?",
        "Answer": "A good rule of thumb is to write short answers to each question — two to three paragraphs would make a good answer. If you go longer, the page will be too long and cluttered."
    },
    {   "id":"7",
        "Question": "What is quantum physics in simple terms?",
       "Answer": "Quantum physics is the study of matter and energy at the most fundamental level. It aims to uncover the properties and behaviors of the very building blocks of nature. While many quantum experiments examine very small objects, such as electrons and photons, quantum phenomena are all around us, acting on every scale."
    },
    {    "id":"8",
        "Question": "Who is the father of quantum physics?",
       "Answer": "Niels Bohr and Max Planck, two of the founding fathers of Quantum Theory, each received a Nobel Prize in Physics for their work on quanta."
    },
    {   "id":"9",
        "Question": "Is quantum physics theory or fact?",
       "Answer": "Quantum theory is the theoretical basis of modern physics that explains the nature and behavior of matter and energy on the atomic and subatomic level. The nature and behavior of matter and energy at that level is sometimes referred to as quantum physics and quantum mechanics."
    },
    { "id":"10",
        "Question": "What is chemistry?",
       " Answer": "Chemistry is the branch of science that deals with the properties, composition, and structure of elements and compounds, how they can change, and the energy that is released or absorbed when they change."
    },
    {"id":"11",
        "Question": "How are chemistry and biology related?",
       "Answer": "Chemistry is the study of substances—that is, elements and compounds—while biology is the study of living things. However, these two branches of science meet in the discipline of biochemistry, which studies the substances in living things and how they change within an organism."
    },
    {"id":"12",
        "Question": "Is chemist a good career?",
       "Answer": "A career as a chemist has good employment opportunities in urban and semi-urban areas. There are negligible opportunities for chemists in rural areas."
    },
    {"id":"13",
        "Question": "What is basic kinematics?",
       "Answer": "Kinematics is the branch of classical mechanics that describes the motion of points, objects and systems of groups of objects, without reference to the causes of motion (i.e., forces ). The study of kinematics is often referred to as the “geometry of motion.” "
    },
    {"id":"14",
       " Question": "What are real life example of kinematics?",
       "Answer": "An orange that falls from a tree. A car moving in a straight line. Firing a cannonball. A car accelerating from zero."
    },
    {"id":"15",
       "Question": "What is basic biology?",
       "Answer": "Biology is the natural science that involves the study of life and living organisms. Without biology, it would be difficult to understand the anatomy of humans, animals, and other creatures."
    },
    {  "id":"16",
       "Question": "What is a cell?",
       "Answer": "In biology, the smallest unit that can live on its own and that makes up all living organisms and the tissues of the body"
    },
    {  "id":"17",
       "Question": "What is life process?",
       "Answer": "The basic processes of life include organization, metabolism, responsiveness, movements, and reproduction. In humans, who represent the most complex form of life, there are additional requirements such as growth, differentiation, respiration, digestion, and excretion. All of these processes are interrelated."
    },
    {"id":"18",
       "Question": "What is the importance of biology?",
       "Answer": "As a field of science, biology helps us understand the living world and the ways its many species (including humans) function, evolve, and interact. Advances in medicine, agriculture, biotechnology, and many other areas of biology have brought improvements in the quality of life."
    },
    { "id":"19",
       "Question": "Who is the father of biology?",
       "Answer": "Aristotle is called the Father of biology. He was a great Greek philosopher and polymath. His theory of biology also known as the “Aristotle's biology” describes five major biological processes, namely, metabolism, temperature regulation, inheritance, information processing and embryogenesis."
    },
    {"id":"20",
        "Question": "What does DNA stand for?",
       "Answer": "Deoxyribonucleic acid (abbreviated DNA) is the molecule that carries genetic information for the development and functioning of an organism. "
    }
    ]
   
  